{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application and more. ",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "Animals",
      "description": "Zoo Animals",
      "id": 3
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "Grizzly Bear",
      "id": 6,
      "back": "Lives in the forest"
    },
    {
      "front": "L",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "Penguin",
      "id": 8,
      "back": "p"
    },
    {
      "front": "Grizzly",
      "id": 9,
      "back": "Forest"
    },
    {
      "front": "Pen",
      "id": 10,
      "back": "stuff"
    },
    {
      "front": "Pen",
      "id": 11,
      "back": "B"
    },
    {
      "front": "P",
      "id": 12,
      "deckId": "3",
      "back": "B"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "front": "Snake",
      "back": "Snek"
    },
    {
      "back": "p",
      "front": "p",
      "deckId": "3",
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "back": "p",
      "front": "e",
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": "dog",
      "back": "cat",
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "pig",
      "back": "piggy",
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "front": "bear",
      "back": "lion",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 18
    }
  ]
}